firedrive.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Firedrive

Your privacy is important to Firedrive Media Limited (“Firedrive”), so we have developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time to reflect our ongoing commitment to the development of new products and services, as well as changes to applicable laws and regulations. Please take time to review our Privacy Policy below and understand how our policies affect you, your personal information and your content.

Firedrive collects personally identifiable information such as your name, name of your business, e-mail address, web site address or URL, home or work address and telephone number. Any and all of this information may also be combined with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.  
As well, Firedrive will also collect financial information including credit card information, email address, billing address, purchases details. Firedrive will submit the information that pertains to payment processing to our payment-processing partners via encrypted communication for verification. Our payment-processing partner keeps the credit card number after processing that allows them to maintain error and transaction logs that make it possible to synchronize credit card information with customer names. Our payment processing partner does not share or sell this information.  It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy of our payment-processing partner to understand how your personal information is collected and use.   
From time to time, Firedrive may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Firedrive may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Firedrive’s products, services, and customer communications.

Firedrive may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. For instance, Firedrive may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone of the user so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.  
Firedrive may also collect information regarding customer activities on our website and other products and services websites advertised on Firedrive.com. This information may be aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

When you sign-up for Firedrive services, we may ask you for personal identifying information including a user name and password. It is your responsibility to keep your user name and password secret and to change it frequently to maintain its security. If you feel your password has been compromised in any way, please contact Firedrive Support. 

Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected through Firedrive.com. This computer-related information includes, without limitation, your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This computer-related information is used by Firedrive for the operation of Firedrive, to maintain quality and to provide general statistics regarding use of Firedrive. We do not share or sell this information to outside parties. 

Firedrive allows you to share information with others publicly which may be indexable by search engines such as Google. Firedrive provides its users with different options for managing your content including sharing and removing content.  As well, Firedrive allows third-party Authorized Agents to monitor all shared content in accordance with the Authorized Agent Removal Policy. 

Firedrive secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Firedrive uses commercially reasonable efforts to secure the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted through Firedrive.com, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

Firedrive.com uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web page in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. When you return to a specific web page on Firedrive.com, the information that you previously provided can be retrieved so that you can easily use Firedrive.com and the features that you customized. For instance, cookies are used to recognize your log-in information for your account so that you do not need to sign-in with each Firedrive session. 

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for Firedrive to disclose your personal information. Firedrive may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms and Conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

If you have registered Firedrive’s products and services, you may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided in your registration or account profile by changing your “account settings.” Firedrive will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

Firedrive will retain your information and files for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with our products and services. If you wish to cancel your Firedrive account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you our products and services, you will be able to deactivate your account on Firedrive.com.  As well, Firedrive shall retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Subject to these requirements, Firedrive will try to delete your information quickly upon deactivation; however, there might be a delay in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. We do not delete from our servers files that you have in common with other users. 

Firedrive does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that a child has provided Firedrive with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us through Firedrive.com’s support ticket system If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

Firedrive websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Firedrive may also use or offer products or services from third parties. Information collected by third parties, including personal information or non-personal information, is governed by their privacy practices. Firedrive is not responsible for use a third-party makes of your information. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

Information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy.

Firedrive regularly reviews our compliance with our Privacy Policy. When a formal written complaint is received, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly. 

By using Firedrive’s products and services, you consent to the collection and use of the information that we collect from you, and that is outlined in this policy. This Privacy Policy may be updated to remain consistent with new products, services, processes, and Internet privacy laws and regulations. By continuing to use Firedrives’s products and services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions or concerns about Firedrives’s Privacy Policy, please contact us through our ticket system at Firedrive.com.

### Head Office

**Firedrive PTE. Ltd.**  
20 Cecil Street, #14-01  
Equity Plaza  
049705   
Singapore

### Regional Support Office

**Firedrive Media Limited  
**13 John Prince’s Street  
4th Floor  
London, W1G 0JR  
England   
1-855-746-7359

Created – August 12, 2013  
Version – February 28, 2014
